<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sriram Narayanan</title>
    <description>Belenix, Continuous Delivery, Cloud, Infrastructure Security</description>
    <link>http://www.sriramnarayanan.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.sriramnarayanan.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 00:43:25 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 00:43:25 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are you Agile?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What does it mean to “be Agile”? Here are my lessons learned by being part of as well as observing Agile projects at ThoughtWorks since Jan 2006.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being Agile means being able to respond to change. The motivation for change could be for business, technical or compliance reasons. Regardless of the reasons, one needs to be able to deliver high value, high quality working software quickly and frequently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fundamentals for being able to this involves
* short feedback loops
* the ability to inspect and adapt
* collaboration and team work&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make these fundamentals happen, are various ceremonies such as “project kickoff”, “release planning”, “daily standups”, “showcases”, “retrospectives”, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These ceremonies are in turn augmented by techniques such as “Iterations”, “User Stories”, “Burn Up/Down charts”, “Test Driven Development”, “Pairing”, “Continuous Integration”, “Planning Poker” etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are ever in doubt on whether you are truly agile or not, ask yourself whether you have the fundamentals listed above in place. Be honest to yourself. If you don’t have the fundamentals in place, then seek help. Remember that a Scrum Certification or a spreadsheet based plan will not make you Agile. Only those fundamentals and practices that enable you to respond to change while delivering high value and high quality working software quickly and frequently will help you be Agile.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 16:51:41 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.sriramnarayanan.com/agile/2016/05/11/on-being-agile.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sriramnarayanan.com/agile/2016/05/11/on-being-agile.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>agile</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moving from LiveJournal</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My earlier blogs can be found &lt;a href=&quot;http://dynamicproxy.livejournal.com&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve decided to move from &lt;a href=&quot;http://livejournal.com&quot;&gt;LiveJournal&lt;/a&gt; to Github Pages using Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learning goals:
- Learn to use Jekyll to understand static site generation.
- Jekyll seems much more flexible as compared to what a paid LiveJournal subscription may provide.
- Learn what it takes to host something like Github pages so that I can provide self-contained Zones in the future.
- Side benefit: Benefit from Github’s CDN + DDOS protection&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 16:51:41 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.sriramnarayanan.com/jekyll/update/2016/02/08/moving-from-livejournal.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.sriramnarayanan.com/jekyll/update/2016/02/08/moving-from-livejournal.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
