<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cd on Sriram Narayanan - The Sky is not the limit</title>
    <link>https://www.sriramnarayanan.com/tags/cd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cd on Sriram Narayanan - The Sky is not the limit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 23:25:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.sriramnarayanan.com/tags/cd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Continuous Delivery happen - ThoughtWorks Talks Tech March 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.sriramnarayanan.com/making-continuous-delivery-happen-thoughtworks-talks-tech-march-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 23:25:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.sriramnarayanan.com/making-continuous-delivery-happen-thoughtworks-talks-tech-march-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I presented on &amp;ldquo;Making CD happen&amp;rdquo; at the ThoughtWorks Talks Tech March 2019 edition at the ThoughtWorks Singapore office&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;embed slideshare&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.slideshare.net/slideshow/embed_code/key/IAdleXumavC1DV&#34; width=&#34;599&#34; height=&#34;487&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; marginwidth=&#34;0&#34; marginheight=&#34;0&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; style=&#34;border:1px solid #CCC;border-width:1px 1px 0;margin-bottom:5px&#34; allowfullscreen webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use slides to support my message, so there is sometimes context around the various slides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the past few years, organisations have been increasingly recognising that along with governance and project management (read, scrum), they need to pay attention to engineering practices too. The result has been an increasting move to achieve  &lt;a href=&#34;https://martinfowler.com/bliki/ContinuousDelivery.html&#34;&gt;Continuous Delivery&lt;/a&gt; (or &amp;ldquo;CI/CD&amp;rdquo; as it is unfortunately often also known).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reality is that the IT budget went into expensive scrum and &amp;ldquo;CI/CD&amp;rdquo; tool implementations, dedicated staff, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a plethora of tools and consultants, lots of tutorials and IT budgets assigned to such initiatives, there are a lot of implementations out there which are not yet delivering results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are still defects in production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is a lot of wait-time between code-commit to go-live&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Triaging defects continues to take time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integration between workstreams continues to be risky&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixing a defect doesn’t guarantee that nothing else got broken&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Changes pushed to prod often leads to failures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What works in one environment doesn’t work in others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>